Carlton Foust Papers, 1959-2003 and undated foustcarlton
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Carlton Foust papers 1959-2003 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Foust, Carlton.
15.0 linear feet 3000 items
Carlton "Butch" Foust was an advertising executive who worked for J. Walter Thompson, Benton & Bowles, McCann-Erickson and other agencies, often in Latin America and Spain.
Collection spans the years 1959-2003 and contains advertising and market research files, client files, brochures, tear sheets, annual reports, case histories, videocassettes, and other files documenting Foust's career as an advertising executive primarily in Latin America and Spain. Materials chiefly relate to Foust's work on behalf of clients such as Kraft Foods, Kellogg, Proctor & Gamble, Coca-Cola, and Unilever, as well as numerous alcoholic beverage companies. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be produced. Contact Research SErvices for more information.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Carlton Foust Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2008.
Collection overview
Collection spans the years 1959-2003 and contains advertising and market research files, client files, brochures, tear sheets, annual reports, case histories, videocassettes, and other files documenting Foust's career as an advertising executive primarily in Latin America and Spain. Materials chiefly relate to Foust's work on behalf of clients such as Kraft Foods, Kellogg, Proctor & Gamble, Coca-Cola, and Unilever, as well as numerous alcoholic beverage companies. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically into seven series: General Files; Account Files; Advertisements; New Business Files; Printed Material; Oversize Material; and Audiovisual Materials.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
J. Walter Thompson Company
Kellogg Company
Kraft Foods Company
Procter & Gamble Company
The Coca-Cola Company
Unilever (Firm).
Advertising agencies -- Spain -- History
Advertising agencies -- United States -- History
Advertising executives
Advertising -- Latin America
Advertising -- Spain
Alcoholic beverage industry
Audiocassettes
Videocassettes
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles Archives
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office Records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Edgar Hatcher Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Victor Guttierez Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. W. Lee Preschel Papers
Charles W. Company Records
Gene Federico Papers
Description of Collection
- General Files, 1959-1994 and undated, 2 boxes
  - Binder--Branding, 1982-1994, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Binder--Concept testing, 1966-1983, 4 folders
  - Binder--Media, 1959-1983 and undated, 3 folders
  - Binder--Promotions, 1969-1985
  - Binder--Promotions, 1969-1985 (Box 2)
  - Binder--Research, 1968-1985, 2 folders
  - Binder--Sales, circa 1960s, 3 folders
  - Brand-building workshop, 1992
  - JWT advertising research, 1980-1985 and undated
  - Market research, 1985-1986, 2 folders
  - Presentation: On Beyond Bite and Smile, undated
  - Slides, undated
- Account Files, 1970-1997 and undated, 5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes planning documents, research reports, brand guidelines, correspondence and other materials relating to the management of advertising account campaigns. Agencies represented include Benton & Bowles (B&B), J. Walter Thompson (JWT), and McCann-Erickson and their various offices and partnerships primarily in Spain, Germany and Latin America. Companies include Kellogg's, Kraft, and Procter & Gamble. Arranged alphabetically by office and client name.
  - Campaign themes and idea starters, undated (Box 3)
  - Benton & Bowles
    - Champion International, 1972
    - General Foods--Carbonated candy (Pop Rocks, Space Dust) review, undated
    - General Foods--Powdered beverage advertising presentation, undated
    - General Foods--U.S. chicken coatings review, undated
    - Procter & Gamble advertising guidelines, 1982
    - Richardson Vick storyboards and cartoons, undated
    - Securities Industry Association, undated
  - B&B Germany
    - Procter & Gamble E34 copy development program, 1982
    - Procter & Gamble storyboard and analysis, undated
  - B&B Italy
    - REEMTSMA new product concepts (tobacco products), 1980
  - B&B/Procter & Gamble
    - Account management, undated
    - Europe--Reports, 1987-1993
    - Germany--Bounce, 1977-1982
    - Germany--Briefing for Ralph Schilling, 1981
    - Reports, 1972-1982, 2 folders
  - B&B/REI (Germany)
    - Budget proposals, 1982-1983
    - Creative review, 1982
  - Clarín (Spain)
    - Associación Nacional de Fabricantes de Cervexa (ANFACE), research, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Coca-Cola España--Fanta situation analysis, 1989-1990, 2 folders
    - William Grant & Sons
      - Cardhu Malt, 1982-1993
      - Glenfiddich, 1992-1993
      - Glenfiddich direct mail, 1993
      - Glenfiddich--Report on Spanish whiskey market, 1993
      - Grant's Whiskey, 1993
      - HIstorical booklet, marketing strategy, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1993
  - Danis B&B (Spain)
    - Photoboards, 1970-1979
  - J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT)
    - Barbara Wingate presentation to Sprint on service brands, 1995
    - Jim Beam marketing plan, 1996, 2 folders
    - Kellogg Company
      - Account manager's guide, 1989 (Box 5)
      - Advertising agency relationship philosophy, 1992
      - Brand equity, 1995
      - Corn Flakes copy strategy, 1996
      - Creative planning guide, 1989
      - Private label study, 1996
      - Product testing guidelines, 1983, 2 folders
      - The Switzerland market, undated
    - Kraft, 1984-1995
    - Strategic planning, 1996
    - Unilever--Media systems development, undated
  - JWT Barcelona
    - Cinzano, 1985-1986
    - Cinzano presentation, 1984
  - JWT/Kellogg (Latin America) communications strategy, 1996-1997
  - JWT/Kraft (Spain)
    - European Mid-Year Creative Review, 1987
    - European Winter Creative Review, 1987, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Slides, undated
  - JWT Ltd. (Asia)--San Miguel Pale Pilsen strategy, 1995
  - JWT London
    - Allied Breweries/Skol presentation and advertising recommendations, 1985
    - Johnnie Walker Scotch
      - Advertising proposals for Europe, 1988
      - Company history booklet, undated
      - Johnnie Walker Red Label, 1985-1986
  - JWT Madrid
    - Johnnie Walker Scotch
      - Johnnie Walker Red Label briefing and evaluation, 1988, 2 folders
      - Research Business International Limited reports
        - Johnnie Walker Red Label Concept Evaluation, 1988
        - The Essence of Johnnie Walker, 1988, 2 folders
      - United Distillers Group--Johnnie Walker European advertisng brief, 1988
    - Scotch whiskey market in Spain, 1988
  - JWT Mexico
    - Kellogg, 1995, 2 folders
  - JWT/Unilever
    - Beating the Superpower, presentation, undated
    - Media buying policy, 1997
    - Reorganization, 1996
  - JWT Venezuela
    - Kellogg new product development, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Kraft advertising, 1996
    - Unilever media review, 1995, 2 folders
  - McCann-Erickson
    - Coca-Cola
      - Coke and food home market promotions, undated
      - Music Strategy Guide, 1989
      - You Can't Beat the Feeling, undated
    - Nestlé communications conference, 1990
    - William Grant & Sons--Glenfiddich in Spain parallel planning, 1993
- Advertisements, 1970s-1995, 2 boxes
  Primarily a clipping file of print advertisements and printed literature for a range of alcoholic beverages. Whiskey and especially Scotch are heavily represented. Arranged alphabetically by beverage.
  - Beer, 1970-1994, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Brandy and cognac, 1980s-1990s, 3 folders
  - Cava, 1980s-1990s
  - Champagne, Jerez, Anis, port, sherry, 1980s-1990s, 2 folders
  - Gin, 1980s-1990s
  - Liqueurs, bitters, aperitifs, vermouth, 1980-1995
  - Vodka, rum, gin, 1980s-1990s, (2 folders)
  - Whiskey
    - Scotch
      - General, 1980s-1990s, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Deluxe scotches, 1980s
      - J&B, 1980s-1990s, 2 folders
      - Johnnie Walker Red Label, 1980s
      - Long John, 1980s
      - Single-malt scotches, 1980s
    - Other whiskeys, 1980s-1990s, 3 folders
  - Wine, 1980s, 2 folders
- New Business Files, 1972-1994 and undated, 2 boxes
  Includes new business pitch presentations, background research and correspondence relating to agency efforts to acquire new advertising accounts. Arranged by agency office and company name.
  - Benton & Bowles
    - Block Drug new product development, 1972 (Box 10)
    - New Business Seminar, 1980, 2 folders
  - Clarín (Spain)
    - Beer articles, 1990-1994, 2 folders
    - Cinnabar--En Mangas de Camisa, 1990
    - Coors
      - Beer articles, 1990-1992, 2 folders
      - Market research and presentation, 1994
      - Presentation, 1994
    - Laboratorios Liade/Boots Company, 1989
    - Memos and miscellaneous, 1986-1993
    - Polygram, 1992-1994
  - J. Walter Thompson Company
    - Kraft new product development, 1978-1993 (Box 11)
    - New business support briefing and work plan, undated
  - JWT Barcelona
    - New business plan, 1986
  - JWT London
    - Philips household appliances, 1986
    - RJR Nabisco, 1988
    - The Winner's Manual; or How to Roll Your Own New Business Presentation, 1981
  - JWT Spain
    - Pirelli, 1984-1985
    - Scotch whiskey articles, 1993
    - Scotch Whiskey Market in Spain, 1985-1993
  - JWT Venezuela
    - Study of alcoholic beverages and rum in Venezuela, 1994
    - Whyte & MacKay--Overview of the Venezuelan spirits market, 1997
  - TBWA Spain
    - Côte d'Or chocolates, 1984
    - Gallina Blanca Purina, 1983
    - Lilly Indiana (OTC analgesics), 1983
    - Sterwin Española (Panadol), 1983
  - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
    - Joe's 70 Secrets for Winning New Business, 1996
- Printed Material, 1959-2003 and undated, 9 boxes
  Includes corporate brochures and booklets, periodical publications, research reports, writings and speeches. Arranged alphabetically by originating organization and title.
  - Advertising Age--Account management workshop, undated (Box 12)
  - Al Ries/Jack Trout--Marketing Warfare, chapter 12, The Beer Wars, 1986
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA)
    - Advertising Agencies, 1976
    - Frederick Gamble--What Advertising Agencies Are, 1959
    - It Works!, 1992
    - John Monsarrat--The Case for the Full-Service Agency, 1971
    - The Advertising Business and Its Career Opportunities, 1961
    - The Value Side of Productivity, 1989
    - Victor Bloede--The Full Service Advertising Agency, 1983
    - What Every Account Executive Should Know About... (pamphlet series), 1990-1994
  - American Business Press--It Pays to Advertise, 1991
  - Asociación Española de Agencias de Publicidad--brochures, 1980s
  - Asociación Europea de Agencias de Publicidad--La Publicidad, undated
  - Bates Worldwide--USP booklets, 1997 and undated
  - BBDO--booklets, 1982 and undated
  - Benton & Bowles (B&B)
    - Al Hampel--Copy Crises and How to Avoid Them, undated
    - Al Hampel--Creative, undated
    - Al Hampel--It's Never Been Done Before..., 1977 and undated, 2 folders
    - B&B Pocketpiece, 1980
    - Charlie Blackmore speech, undated
    - Coupons, Samples or Sweepstakes?, undated
    - DMB&B Italy, undated
    - International Copy Adaptation, undated
    - It's Not Creative Unless It Sells, undated
    - Jim Tappen speech, 1977
    - Profile of an Advertising Agency, 1982
    - Profile of an International Advertising Agency, undated
    - Training Manual, undated, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Transnational Satellite Broadcasting in Europe, undated
    - Victor Bloede--Some Thoughts about Benton & Bowles, undated
    - Victor Bloede speech to ANA, 1977
  - B&B International--Brochure, undated
  - B&B Ltd.--Roo Meadows, They Consume Advertising Too, 1982
  - Boston Consulting--Bruce Henderson, Why the (Smart) Rich Get Richer, 1994
  - BRX Global--Brand Equity Systems, undated
  - Carvis Needham--Booklet, circa 1984
  - Center for Advertising Services (CAS)
    - Beer Promotions, 1993
    - Charles Mittelstadt--Brand Franchise-Building, 1993
    - How Retailers Promote to Attract and Keep Customers, 1993
    - Janet Jacquette--U.S. Cigarette Market, 1993
    - Jeremy Steinman--What's Ahead for the American Beer Industry in the 90s, 1990
    - Joan Leake--U.S. Baked Goods Market, 1993
    - Joan Leake--U.S. Market for Side Dishes, 1992
    - Joan Leake--U.S. Salty Snack Market, 1993
    - Joan Leake--U.S. Supermarkets, 1993
    - John Bergin--American Brewers' Dilemma: Flat Beer Advertising, undated
    - Linda Lagomarsino--U.S. Laundry Detergent Market, 1993
    - Margie Braimon--U.S. Beer Market, 1992
    - Margie Rizika--Sports Marketing, 1993
    - Margie Rizika--U.S. Amusement Parks, 1993
    - Margie Rizika--U.S. Athletic Footwear Market, 1992
    - Margie Rizika--U.S. Beer Market, 1992-1993
    - Margie Rizika--U.S. Lottery Market, 1992
    - Margie Rizika--U.S. Wine Market, 1992
    - McCollum Spielman--Comparative Advertising in the U.S., 1991
    - Mona Doyle--Changing Relationships of Consumers and Brands, 1993
    - Robin Feuerstein--U.S. Cough and Cold Remedies, 1992
    - Robin Feuerstein--U.S. Facial Skin Care Market, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Robin Feuerstein--U.S. Hand and Body Lotion Market, 1993
    - Robin Feuerstein--U.S. Shampoo and Conditioner Market, 1993
    - Robin Feuerstein--U.S. Toilet Soap Market, 1993
    - Sharon Reinhack--U.S. Beverage Trends, 1992
  - Cinzano--various speeches, 1985
  - Classic Malts Society-- Sláinte newsletter, undated
  - Consumer Response Corporation--Concept Testing vol. 3, 1985
  - Dancer Fitzgerald Sample--Booklets, circa 1982
  - Danis (Spain)--House advertisements, undated
  - Danis B&B (Spain)
    - Brochure, circa 1967
    - Cómo Creamos para Tang una Nueva Categorio de Producto, undated
    - Profile of a Spanish Advertising Agency (English and Spanish versions), 1978
    - Quienes Somos, undated
  - Direccion General de Medios de Communicacion Social--Cómo Contrar la Publicidad de una Forma Profesional y Eficaz, 1987
  - Domecq--Wine and brandy brochures, 1988 and undated
  - Firestarter--20 Ways to Make a Better Presentation, undated
  - FMRG (Spain)--Booklet, undated
  - Foote Cone & Belding--Booklets, undated
  - General Foods Europe--Advertising Principles and Guidelines, 1979
  - Google.com--Brochure and printout, 2003
  - Grey Advertising--Booklets, 1984-1986
  - Howard Morgens--Advertising from a Management Standpoint, 1960
  - Interpublic--Philip Geier: Where Do We Go from Here?, 1992
  - Jack Daniel Distillery--Small Batch Bourbon Collection mailing, 1992
  - Johnnie Walker--Advertising postcards, undated
  - Johns Hopkins School of Public Health--How to Select and Work with an Advertising Agency, 1996
  - Juego de la Compra (game), undated
  - J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT)
    - Account Manager's Handbook, undated (Box 15)
    - Advertising, recruitment brochure, undated
    - Advertising Planning Methods, 1987
    - Advertising to Children, 1987
    - Banesco case history, circa 1991
    - Beating the Superpower (P&G) presentation, undated
    - Burt Manning--Creating Maximum Bandwidth, 1995
    - Buying--It's Not an Event, It's a System, 1994
    - Criteria for Selecting a Worldwide Agency, undated
    - Dan Seymour--Change and Challenge, undated
    - Denis Lanigan--What is Multinationality? Can It Be Cured?, 1983
    - Eduardo Parra--Glosario Publicitario Español-Inglès/Inglès-Español, undated
    - El Manuel para Cuentos de JWT, 1987
    - El Manuel para Medios de JWT, undated
    - Guia para la Realización de un Spot Publicitario, undated
    - J. Walter Thompson, Advertising Agent, 1978
    - Kellogg's Brand Equity, undated (Box 16)
    - La Guia para Investigacion de JWT, circa 1987
    - Looking Up at JWT (guide for dealing with superiors), 1992
    - Martin Sorrell presentation, 1996
    - Oh.what//a.tangled.web//we.weave.net (guide to Internet use), circa 1995
    - People Buy Brands, Not Products, 1994
    - Some Things We Have Learned About Managing a JWT Office, undated
    - The Many Worlds of Sam Meek, 1981
    - The Thompson Way, 1987, (2 folders)
    - Thompson Red Book (reissue), 1899
    - Thompson Total Branding, 1996
    - Total Branding case histories, undated
    - Worldwide Office Address List, 1995
  - JWT Detroit--FOB Detroit, 1966
  - JWT Europe--Lux brand strategy, 1992
  - JWT Hong Kong--T-Plans and Planning Cycle, 1985
  - JWT/Kellogg
    - Kellogg's Better Breakfast, undated, 2 folders
    - Promotion Ideas, 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - JWT Korea--Unilever, In Pursuit of Excellence, 1995
  - JWT/Lever--What Should We Do about Fabric Care within Our Portfolio? (Fabric care exploratory), undated
  - JWT London
    - Acorn to Zapping (glossary), 1987
    - An Approach to New Business, 1988
    - Credentials Presentation for Smaller Clients, 1988
    - Getting the Best, 1987
    - I Hear What You Say..., 1972
    - Issue--Marketing to Women, 1987
    - Jack Cronin--Future Trends in Advertising, 1985
    - Jeremy Bullmore--Archimedes and the Efficacy of Prayer, undated
    - John Maddel--Where Do Successful Brands Come From?, undated
    - Judy Lannon--Humanistic Advertising, 1983
    - Lux Brand Development, 1990
    - The King Papers, 1988
  - JWT New York--A Guide to the JWT T-Plan, 1978
  - JWT Online--Slow Traffic Keep Right (Internet glossary), 1994
  - JWT Spain
    - El Mercado y Nuestros Anuncios, undated
    - Historia Incompleta de Slogans, Lemas, etc., 1980
    - Jaime Sáinz de la Maza--¿Cómo Preparamos la Publicidad de Mañana?, 1988
    - Julian Bravo--En Defensa de la Publicidad, 1977
    - Julian Bravo--J. Walter Thompson España de 1927 a 1936, 1985
    - Julian Bravo--Reflexiones sobre Nuestra Oficio Publicitario, undated
    - JWT España, 1979
    - La Casa de Herramientos, 1988
    - Las Nuevas Palabras de la Publicidad y la Tecnologia, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Review of Spanish Whiskey Market, circa 1992
  - JWT/Unilever
    - Detergents 101, 1996
    - Media Systems, undated
  - JWT West, Change newsletter, 1995-1996
  - Kraft Jacobs Suchard--Best Practices in Advertising Development, undated
  - Leo Burnett--Booklets, 1981
  - Longman-Moran--William Moran, Conceptual Framework for Brand Equity Measurement and Management, 1993
  - Maxwell Dane (DDB)--15%: Fact or Fiction?, 1966
  - McCann-Erickson
    - A Brand Is a Curious Beast, undated
    - A World of Difference, undated
    - Marcio Moreira--What Does a Creative Director Do, Anyway?, undated
    - Robert James--The Pendulum Must Swing Back!, 1992
    - The Beer Market in Spain, 1992
    - World; La Razón y la Pasión, undated
  - Messel--Peter Miller, The Outlook for Diamonds, 1987
  - Metra/Seis
    - Beer study, 1990
    - European beer study--Spain, 1989-1990, 2 folders
    - General Foods/Chicle study, 1976 (Box 19)
  - MKT (Marketing Telefonico)--Su Guia de Marketing Telefonico, undated
  - Needham Harper--Paul Harper, A Word or Two about Advertising, undated
  - Needham International--Pamphlet, undated
  - Nestlé--Camillo Pagano, Corporate Perspective, undated
  - Newspaper Association of America--Advertising Pocket Guide, undate
  - N.W. Ayer--Ayer Plan, Strategic Planning for Human Contact, 1981
  - Odec--Tables on Beer Consumption in Spain, 1992
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Booklets, circa 1983
  - PACT--Positioning Advertising Copy Testing, 1982
  - Peter Rogen and Associates--Effective Presentation Skills, 1984
  - Philip Fitzell/Charles Mittelstadt--The Growing Power of Private Labels, undated
  - Quest and Associates--Relationship Marketing; What Is the Future of Advertising; Understanding the MTV Generation; NIghtmare on Main Street (private label brands), 1992-1993
  - Recipe cards, undated
  - Saab--Graphic Guidelines, 1990
  - SSC&B Lintas--Booklet,undated
  - Scotch whiskey miscellaneous brochures, 1986 and undated
  - SPEA--Training Manual, 1968-1969, 2 folders
  - Stephen Fossler Company--Guide to Planning and Promoting Your Business Anniversary, 1999
  - TBWA--Booklets, 1982
  - True North Communications--Booklet, 1995
  - Unilever
    - Good Advertising Practice, undated (Box 20)
    - Shaping for Outstanding Performance, undated
  - Various
    - Account planning, 1982-1988
    - Agency compensation articles, 1964-1988
    - Agency evaluation guidelines, 1974-1994
    - Case histories--Dawn, Pledge, undated
    - Corporate Advertising, 1985 and undated
    - New product development, 1972-2003
    - Personnel issues: Hiring and evaluation, 1976-1979 and undated
    - Transnational advertising agencies, undated
    - World Brands, 1985-1986
  - Wall Street Journal--Why Advertise?, 1991
  - Wood Brigale--The Instrument of Advertising, 1978
  - WPP--World Ownership Plan, 1997
  - Yellowhammer Advertising--Booklets, circa 1989
  - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)--Booklet, 1981
- Oversize Materials, (3 boxes)
  - Account Files: JWT/Kraft concept advertisements, undated (Box 21)
  - Printed Material: Asociacion Equatoriana de Agencias de Publicidad--Tres Decadas de la Publicidad en el Equador, 1996
  - Printed Material: Backer Spielvogel Bates--Booklet, undated
  - Printed Material: BBDO 1891, 100th anniversary booklet, 1991
  - Printed Material: Grey Advertising--Booklet, circa 1981
  - Printed Material: Anuncios (Spain)--Ranking de Agencias '93, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Printed Material: Daniel Solana--Creatas y Ejecutas: Storieta Board de una Agencia de Publicidad (comic book), 1989
  - Printed Material: Gebrüder Jllert Gmbh--Jllbert Etiketten: Die Vorbildliche Flaschenausstattung (book of wine labels), circa 1952
  - Printed Material: JWT/Kraft--Veinte Años in España, 1988
  - Printed Material: JWT Venezuela--House advertisement, 1964
  - Account files--Benton & Bowles, S.C. Johnson Glade animation frame and storyboard, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Advertisements: Simmenthal (Tonno, Brodo Tanto Gusto); REEMTSMA R6 (tobacco product), 1973 and undated
  - B&B Italy, staff photograph, undated
- Audiovisual Materials, (1 box)
  Access Restrictions
  Original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be produced. Contact Research Services for further information.
  - Anuncios de Estudiantes. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00. (Box 24)
  - Benton & Bowles--S.C. Johnson Bravo floor wax: Clean Floor. 1970. Audio reel. TRT: 4:00. (2 reels)
  - Clarín (Spain)--Estudiantes. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 1:40.
  - Close Up. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00.
  - Danis B&B--Agrupación Aseguradores de Vida: Unete a la Gente Segura. 1978. 7" vinyl record. TRT: 6:30.
  - JWT Atlanta--United States Marine Corps: Sword, Knight, Chess. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 1:30